# Afonso Pinto

Sintra, Lisboa +351 912 008 773 Afonso.pinto2710@hotmail.com



### **Short introduction**

Hi, my name is Afonso and I am currently a Full stack. Net developer working at Fegime Portugal.

Working with IT since 2021, most of this time spent as a Full-Stack developer. Always curious and eager to learn.

I Finished a Management and Programming of Computer Systems course in 2021 and since then I have always kept self-learning in multiple fields related to programming. Today I can say that I have developed from scratch to finish two webapps in which multiple users rely every day.

### **Education**

## LEVEL IV TECHNICAL COURSE | 2021 | ESCOLA SECUNDÁRIA LEAL DA CÂMARA

· Management and programming of computer systems

# **Experience**

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER | WEB & GAMBLE | MAY 2021 - JULY 2021

 Development of a webapp that creates custom bills and manages the company data Technologies used: PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS

#### WEB DESIGNER | DIGITAL XPERIENCE | OCTOBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

 Design of websites with WordPress and CSS Technologies used: WordPress, CSS, Elementor

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER | FEGIME | JANUARY 2022 - TODAY

- $\cdot\,$  Development of a .Net we bapp that makes the company ecosystem of data much more accessible within the whole group
- Management of company data
  Technologies used: C#, .NET CORE, SQL, SAP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS